[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Prewitt squares off with \u201cFatso\u201d Borgnine in a back-ally knife fight and avenges Maggio\u2019s murder in this 1953 movie.", "correct_answer": "From Here to Eternity", "incorrect_answers": ["Bridge Over the River Kwai", "The Hustler", "On the Waterfront"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All the actors who portrayed Vito Corleone won an Oscar.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Your physician has ordered an electroencephalogram (EEG), the graphic recording of the electrical activity of what organ?", "correct_answer": "Brain", "incorrect_answers": ["Muscles", "Liver", "Heart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The planet Jupiter was named after the chief God in Roman Mythology. What is the name of his Greek counterpart?", "correct_answer": "Zeus", "incorrect_answers": ["Apollo", "Ares", "Hara"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This cell structure exists only when the long pieces of Deoxyribonucleic acid (DNA), called chromosomes, replicate themselves.", "correct_answer": "chromatid", "incorrect_answers": ["flagelle", "centrosome", "microtubule"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Australian pop duo performed the 1990s hit To the Moon and Back?", "correct_answer": "Savage Garden", "incorrect_answers": ["The Seekers", "Soundgarden", "INXS"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is written on a sign near Sheks home in the 2001 animated comedy movie Shrek?", "correct_answer": "Beware the Ogre!", "incorrect_answers": ["Home, Smelly Home", "Welcome To My Dirty Estate!", "Dont Wipe Your Feet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these dog breeds originated in Hungary?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Pumi", "Puli", "Mudi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are twelve apples on a table. You take four. How many apples do you have now?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["12", "8", "0"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are 20 consonants in the English alphabet.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what part of the human body is the bundle of His located?", "correct_answer": "Heart", "incorrect_answers": ["Lungs", "Testicles", "Brain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lucille, the slightly psychotic science fair judge from the movie Meet the Robinsons, had invented a caffeine path that equaled how many cups of coffee each?", "correct_answer": "12", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "4", "15"]}]